celebritystyleguide.com 2018-12-24

# Privacy Statement | Celebrity Style Guide

Privacy Statement 

Thank you for visiting www.CelebrityStyleGuide.com, a place where people who are passionate about celebrity and designer fashion and accessories come together to share their opinions and discoveries. The services offered by CelebrityStyleGuide.com (our Site) are made available by Celebrity Style Guide (CelebrityStyleGuide, we or us). 

We appreciate the opportunity to interact with you on the Internet and are committed to protecting and safeguarding your privacy. The purpose of this Privacy Statement is to inform you about the types of information we might collect about you when you visit our Site, how we may use that information, whether we disclose it to anyone, and the choices you have regarding our use of, and your ability to correct, that information. 

What Information We Collect and How We Use It   
Any information we collect on our Site generally falls into the following two categories: Personally Identifiable Information or Aggregate Information. 

1\. Personally Identifiable Information   
This refers to information that lets us know who you are or things specifically about you. 

A. Visitors   
You can browse our Site without revealing any Personally Identifiable Information.   
B. Registration   
If you want to register and interact with our Site, you may voluntarily provide Personally Identifiable Information (such as User Name, e-mail address, Birth Date and Country) to be used for the purpose of communications with you, including via e-mail, to assist with registration information. We use this information to provide better service in the event that you contact us again. We may share your email information only with our advertising entities, as stated below.   
C. Surveys and Promotions   
From time to time you may voluntarily provide Personally Identifiable Information to complete surveys and questionnaires or to participate in user polls. We use this information to improve our Site and services. We may also use your Personally Identifiable Information to provide you newsletters. We may share your email information only with our advertisers in order for them to send you promotional email that is pertinent to the products and context of our web site. 

2\. Aggregate Information   
This refers to information that does not, by itself, identify you as a specific individual. Such information would include the Uniform Resource Locator ("URL") of the Web site that referred you to our Site, your Internet Protocol ("IP") address (a number automatically assigned to your computer whenever you surf the Web), your operating system and browser type, and any search terms that you enter on our Site. Our Web server aggregates this information in order to monitor the level of activity on our Site, evaluate its effectiveness, and improve the content of our Site in order to make your visit an easy and enjoyable experience. 

We may collect, compile, store, publish, promote, report, or otherwise disclose or use any Aggregate Information, provided that such information does not personally identify you. We do not correlate any Personally Identifiable Information with the Aggregate Information that we collect on our Site. If we do correlate any Aggregate Information to you, it will be protected like any other Personally Identifiable Information under this Privacy Statement. 

Sharing Your Information   
Except as disclosed in this Privacy Statement, we do not sell, trade, rent, or otherwise retransmit any Personally Identifiable Information we collect online unless we have your permission. Any Personally Identifiable Information you provide to us will be stored in our databases in the United States. 

3\. General   
In the event of a court order, subpoena, or government investigation, we reserve the right to release Personally Identifiable Information. We also reserve the right to release Personally Identifiable Information when we believe that such release is reasonably necessary to enforce or apply our Terms of Use or to protect the rights, property, and safety of others and ourselves. 

Should Celebrity Style Guide or its related entities merge with or be acquired by another business entity, or its respective assets be acquired, you should expect that we would share some or all of your Personally Identifiable Information to companies assuming the role of serving you and other users of our Site. 

Your Choices   
Your permission is always secured first. We will not use or share the Personally Identifiable Information collected on our Site in ways unrelated to the purpose for which you provided the information, including those described above, without providing you a choice whether to permit any such unrelated uses. 

Accessing and Correcting Your Information   
We take reasonable measures to ensure that any Personally Identifiable Information we collect on our Site is accurate, current, complete, and reliable for its intended use. If you wish to update or otherwise correct Personally Identifiable Information you have provided to us, you may edit your information online after completing registration, or contact us as described in the "Contact Us" section, below, and we will assist you. 

Protecting Your Information   
We acknowledge your trust and are committed to take reasonable steps to protect Personally Identifiable Information you provide online from loss, misuse, and unauthorized access. We employ physical, electronic, and managerial processes to safeguard and secure your information. 

It is your responsibility to safeguard the password you use to access our Site, and to promptly advise Celebrity Style Guide if you ever suspect that your password has been compromised. We strongly encourage you to change your password regularly to prevent unauthorized access. Because your user name and password are specific to you, you acknowledge sole responsibility for any and all use of our Site conducted with your user name and password. 

Use of Cookies On This Site   
A "cookie" is a small data file transferred to your computer's hard drive that allows a Web site to respond to you as an individual, gathering and remembering information about your preferences in order to tailor its operation to your needs, likes and dislikes. Overall, cookies are safe, as they only identify your computer to customize your Web experience. Accepting a cookie does not provide us access to your computer or any Personally Identifiable Information about you, other than the information you choose to share. Other servers cannot read them, nor can they be used to deliver a virus. 

Most browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually adjust yours (Microsoft Internet Explorer or Netscape Navigator) to notify you of cookie placement requests, refuse certain cookies, or decline cookies completely. If you turn off cookies completely, there may be some Web site features that will not be available to you, and some Web pages may not display properly. 

To support the personalized features of our Site we must send a cookie to your computer's hard drive and/or use cookie-based authentication to identify you as a registered Site user. We DO NOT, however, use so-called "surveillance" cookies that track your activity elsewhere on the Web. 

Links To Other Web Sites   
Links to third-party Web sites may be provided solely for your information and convenience, or to provide shopping for various goods and services through our Merchant and Services Partners. If you use these links, you will leave our Site. This Privacy Statement does not cover the information practices of those Web sites linked to our Site, nor do we control their content or privacy policies. We suggest that you carefully review the privacy policies of each site you visit. 

Children's Privacy Protection   
We take special care to protect the privacy needs of children and encourage parents to be an active participant in their child's online activities. Our Site does not target and is not intended for children under the age of 16, and we will not knowingly collect Personally Identifiable Information from them. If we discover personal data from a child through our Site, we will eliminate that data. 

Changes To This Statement   
Any updates or changes to the terms of this Privacy Statement will be posted here on our Site and the date of the newest version posted below. Please check back frequently, especially before you submit any Personally Identifiable Information at our Site, to see if this Privacy Statement has changed. By using our Site, you acknowledge acceptance of this Privacy Statement in effect at the time of use. 

Contact Us   
If you have any concerns about our use of your information or about this Privacy Statement, please send an e-mail to support@celebritystyleguide.com. We will make every reasonable effort to address your concerns and remedy any problems you bring to our attention. 

AFFILIATES   
Celebrity Style Guide is affiliated with RewardStyle. This means that Celebrity Style Guide will periodically post on products through affiliation links provided. In return Celebrity Style Guide may receive a small commission for purchases associated with that link (i.e., a percentage of the sales price of sales originating from the linked product). So, if you click on a link and make a purchase from an affiliate site, there are some instances where we may make a commission from your purchase. Not all of the products we link are through the affiliate program and the affiliate program does not affect what we choose to cover in our posts. All of the items we choose to blog about are genuinely things that we like and want to share. 

Readers: Celebrity Style Guide will not accept any products or sponsored posts from companies that we would not otherwise post about. All opinions are our own and will be written to reflect our true thoughts. Any posts that are sponsored will be disclosed as a sponsored post. Moreover, any products which have been gifted or provided gratis to Celebrity Style Guide shall be noted with c/o (courtesy of) or gifted at the bottom of the post and are only posted if we believe they are a good fit for the Celebrity Style Guide aesthetic and content. 

Updated October 13, 2014. 

© 2005-2014 Celebrity Style Guide, Inc., U.S.A, all rights reserved.
